the Ingush were taken away from their lands Yes their
у ингушей забрали ихние земли Да ихние
houses Hello hello hello
дома Здравствуйте здравствуйте
I am from the city of Khmelniki
здравствуйте Я из города хмельники
Ki city Vladikavkaz this is North
кий города Владикавказ это Северная
Ossetia this is North Ossetia yes yes the
Осетия это Северная Осетия да да
Ossetians are prepared inshi oti inshi
подготовлены осетины инши оти инши
Ossetians Well, this is a bearded insha
осетин Ну это бородатый
This is an insult And what an insult is the
инша Это оскорбление А что оскорбление е
stones yes well Well, these are friendly
камени да так Ну это же дружественные
people  Axis Ingush they live there peacefully I
народ оси ингуши они споко там живут
live No they are never friends they are enemies
живу Нет они никогда не друже это враги
Well don’t
Ну не
say don’t say enemies but well in short they are not
говори не говори враги но ну короче не
enemies but Ingush and Aspens hate each other
враги но ингуши и осины друг друга
Well what are you saying but that’s exactly what
ненавидят ну что ты говоришь а точно это
happened Suburban district also they
ж то было Пригородный район тоже там
killed Ingush there they killed Ingush  Ossetians are
убивали ингуша убивали ингуша осетины
definitely Ossetians, it’s definitely Ossetians, it’s the
точно осетины точно это осетины это
Ingush who killed the
ингуши убивали
Ingush, they expelled them from the suburban area, it’s
ингушей изгнали из пригородного района
definitely that no one expelled the Ingush children, they
точно то ингушей никто не изгонял детей
killed them now,
убивали сечас
look, the
смотри
year is not ninety-
год не девяносто
two Yes, there is, here there is,
второе Да вот есть вот
firstly,
есть во-первых
Vova rci of the Ingush, and in the ninety-second
Вовы рци ингушей а В девяносто втором в
day, pogroms of expulsion Yes  pogrom
дено вром погромы изгнания Да погром
expulsion Yes, those who died from their territories of
изгнание Да погибшие своих территорий
exile From which of
изгнания С каких это
their own died 33
своих погибло 33
Ingush so 12 children under 15
ингушки так 12 детей до 15 лет
died And how many died And how
погибли А сколько погиб А сколько
many how many Well, there is no Wikipedia
сколько ну Википедии нету
so 608 people polo 490 Ingush and 118
так 608 человек поло 490 ингушей и 118
Otin who whom
отин кто кого
Istra here on Wikipedia go to Wikipedia right now
Истре вот в Википедии зайди прямо сейчас
your Russians here is a link the
Википедию ши ваши российские тут ссылка
newspaper of lime
газета
publishes what
извести публикует что ещ
else General Prosecutor's Office
е Генеральная прокуратура
Roy were destroyed from the suburban area
Рой уничтожены из сл пригородного района
in which they lived
в которых проживали
Why They were destroyed, the meaning was
ин Почему Они уничтожены были смыс
destroyed people live now Ingush
уничтожены живут люди сейчас ингуши в
including Which ones were destroyed So why was the
том числе Какие уничтожены Так почему
memory destroyed No one will
уничтожили паму уничтожили никто не
destroy say I'm asking you Here
уничтожит говори я вас спрашиваю Вот
look, North Ossetia honored the memory of the
смотри Северной Осетии почтили память
victims of the
жертв
conflict, here is the article
конфликта вот статья
right And you burn the streets correctly, he opened it, he
правильно он открыл он правильны он
opened it correctly Wikipedia Wikipedia will actually be
открыл Википедию Википедии реально будет
written that it’s clear that I’m
написано то что понятно дело что мне
interested in why it’s written like that, there are
интересно почему так написано так там
links directly to real
ссылки прямо на реальные материалы
Russian materials Well, this is complete nonsense Well, how
российские Ну это бред полный Ну как
complete nonsense I don’t want to let you
полный Я не хочу давайте вы будете
argue about this now Lord
сейчас это спорить Господи
No So why did they expel the Ingush From their
Нет Так А за что изгнали ингушей С ихних
villages of relatives From their villages of relatives of all
сёл родных С ихних сёл родных всех
relatives with Which Stalin was expelled by Stalin
родных с Какие Сталин изгнали Сталин
Inga not In the ninety-second year, here are 13
Ингу не В девяносто втором году вот 13
of the n villages of the suburban DISTRICT in which it
из п сёл пригородного РАЙОНО в которых
is compact  lived the Ingush were
компактно проживали ингуши были
exterminated the Ingush were
уничтожены ингуши были
exterminated
уничтожены
Well, they drove me Well, I mean, now the
Ну загнали Ну в смысле сейчас же живут
Ingush live in a suburban area, as far as I
ингуши в пригородном районе насколько я
know Well, now the Jews live in Germany Yes,
знаю Ну так сейчас и евреи в Германии
but Hitler exterminated the Jews
живут Да но Гитлер истреблял евреев
exterminated the Jews Well, yes, well, yes,
истреблял евреев Ну да Ну ну да а в чём
that’s what was funny  Why were the Ingush
было Вот в чём прикол зачем ингушей
expelled from the suburban district of the district?
изгнали из пригородного района района их
No one expelled them. Stalin expelled them,
никто не изгонял их ещё Сталин изгнал
then they returned and they began to
потом они вернулись и они стали
demand back to their Prigorodny
требовать обратно в свой Пригородный
district. So wait, yes, that is, Stalin
район Так подожди да то есть Сталин их
deported them, then they returned, there is a
депортировал потом ээ вернулись есть
decree of the RSFSR back under Yeltsin, and
постановление РСФСР ещё при ельцине да о
about the return of all this  peoples Yes,
ээ возвращении всем этим народам Да
their property about rehabilitation Yes, and the
ихнего имущества о реабилитации Да также
Crimean Tatars returned to Crimea
Крымские татары в Крым вернулись Да
Yes, the Chechens returned to Chechnya Yes, well,
чеченцы в Чечню вернулись Да ну а на
who lives on their territories? Well,
ихних территориях кто жи кто живёт Ну ну
they also settled
и они тоже селились
there legally and
там на законных основаниях и до
lived there until the ninety-second year. Why were
девяносто второго года жили там А почему
they expelled?  no one expelled them They wanted
изгнали их никто не изгонял Они хотели
more, they lived normally in the sense They
большего они нормально жили в смысле Они
still live here, I mean,
до сих пор здесь живут поди то есть
the girl opened Wikipedia the girl I
девушка же открыла Википедию девушка Я
didn’t wander, you saw it
же не брел вы видели там
written there Written No, well, how did it all start
написано Написано Не ну как всё началось
That’s
Вот
who started it all That’s the same question
это кто всё начал Вот и в этом же вопрос
so again it started didn’t start, I see Yes,
так ещё раз начал не начал вот я вижу Да
500 Ingush were killed and expelled and
500 ингушей убито да изгнаны да
destroyed 13 villages, how is it who destroyed
уничтожены 13 сёл как это кто уничтожал
villages with Ingush villages with
сёла с ингушами сёла с
Ingush no one
ингушами никто их не
destroyed them, the same is written nothing,
уничтожал то же написано ничтоже
nothing is written Well, it is written, the
написано ничтоже Ну написано написано
dead Ingush were buried in a
вот погибших ингушей захоронили на
cemetery in Nazran  in 2012, a
кладбище в назране в 2012 году здесь был
memorial was opened here in memory of the victims of the autumn of
открыт мемориал памяти жертв осени
ninety-two from the second
девяносто второго года со второго
year, poor
года бедные
Ingush Well, yes And how many Ingush
ингуши Ну да А сколько ингушей
to shoot about the network is not indicated anywhere Yes, well, it
перестреливать о сети нигде не указано
is not indicated there and it is not indicated there, and
Да ну там не указано а там не указано да
what is not indicated there as Ingush
то что там же не указывается как ингуши
from under  Tishka is being killed there, how many stories
из-под Тишка убивают там сколько историй
? Yes, it’s also indicated there. But it’s just
Да там же указано Вот только а то это
some Ingush from the underworld who killed something.
какие-то ингуши из подтишка убивали
Yes, they killed something. Yes, but what’s
что-то Да убивали что-то
not indicated there is that
Да а не указано там то что
terrorist attacks would be
теракты бы
Alan, what would not be,
Алан то что нет
look according to the data of the Federal
смотри по данным Федеральной
Migration Service of Russia in  In Ingushetia there
миграционной службы России в ингушети
were up to 46,000 officially
было до 46.000 официально
registered Ingush internally
зарегистрированных ингушских внутренне
displaced persons, that is, expelled from
перемещенных лиц то есть изгнанных из
their territories Yes, in North Ossetia there are
своих территорий Да в Северной Осетии
approximately 46,000, that is, you expelled
вот приго 46000 то есть вы изгнали
46,000 people
46.000 людей
[music]
[музыка]
Ingush deno
ингушей
per year Yes, [ __ ] up you didn’t know, you
дено в год Да [__] наху вы не знали
didn’t know I don’t
ёпта не знали Я не
know Please Wikipedia  e noma there
знаю Прошу Википедию е нома там же
Wikipedia yes The girl can find
Википедия да Девушка же может найти
can find you didn’t know about this I’ll
может найти вы не знали об этом сес
hear
услышу
everything for the first time Why condemn conflicts well
всё Зачем конфликты осуждать хорошо вот
here we come home
й домой приехали
and how it turns out look at the Ingush they
а как получается вот смотрите у ингушей
took away their lands Yes their
забрали ихние земли Да ихние
houses their lands Their houses on the territory of
дома их земли ихние дома на территории
Ossetia  once again on the territory Look,
Осетии ещё раз на территории Вот смотри
they lived there was no state Ossetia
они жили не было государства Осетия Да
Yes, there was no state Ingushetia Yes,
вот и не было государствен Ингушетия Да
for example, there was Russia Yes, there
вот например была Россия Да там
lived Ingush villages and Ossetian villages
жили ингушские сёла были и осетинские
and the Inshis,
да инши
accept
прини
the truth there, like the Ossetians, like the Ossetians
там правда как и осетины как и осетины
Well, who expelled the Inshes  you say
Ну так а кто изгнал инше вы говорите
like the land is not theirs, the land expelled when
типа не ихняя земля земля изгнал когда
the second time or the first time and forty-four and
второй раз или первый раз и сорок четв и
ninety-day forty why did Stalin
девяносто дено соро чем же Сталин их
send them along with the Chechens I In the
отправил вместе с чеченцами я В
ninety-
девяносто
second from this year it became the land and
втором с этого года это стали земли
you in the forty-fourth year together with
ь вы в сорок четвёртом году вместе со
Stalin it turns out
сталином получается
[  music]
[музыка]
pakovannya ninety-second year So
паковання девяносто второй год Так
wait, you said that the Ingush are enemies
подожди это ты сказал что ингуши враги
You started it, Zubastic started that the Ingush are
Ты же начал ты Зубастик начал что ингуши
enemies Zubastic Yes, I remembered That’s it
враги Зубастик Да я вспомнил Вот это
[music] yes
[музыка]
You’re in for
да Тебе за
the kill Well, I’m for the truth I’m for
забить Ну я за правду Я за
the truth Well, go for your great Well  look
правду Ну иди на за сво пра Ну смотри а
Where are you running away Yeah, that's it damn it, who is
Куда ты убегаешь Ага вот так блин кто у
watching from the Ingushetia? Yes, put
нас смотрит из ингушетий Да поставьте
a plus sign
плюсик
like that, that's all in short Russian is
вот так вот и вся короче Российская это
Ossetian they always smile
Осетинская они всегда улыбаются
smiling Ingush enemies Ingush enemies
улыбаются ингуши враги ингуши враги
evicted them From their historical
выселили их С ихних исторических
territories Yes, where they lived from
территорий Да где они жили и спокон
time immemorial Write to  miy Telegram directly at once axis
веков Пиши на мий Telegram прямо зараз
VN
ось ВН
apok tse more and more respectfully YouTube
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the skarg ORV into your ban and
загоняя нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и
even more videos I don’t show
дуже багато видео не показую
people at the moment I don’t show information about
людям вчасно не показуе информация про
streams for that for this purpose mi Mali
стримы тому для того щоб ми Мали
operational link to write directly for
оперативный звязок пишиться прямо за а
apok there in telegra  okm video also tezh
пок там в телегра окм видео ще теж
tsikava and korisna information and mi vinni
цикава и корисна информация и ми повинни
z you trimati postiyny operational
з вами тримати постийний оперативный
connection
звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine letter
YouTube Слава Украине пись
E
E